<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Settings on</title><link>https://javireguera.github.io/docs/settings/</link><description>Recent content in Settings on</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://javireguera.github.io/docs/settings/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Global settings</title><link>https://javireguera.github.io/docs/settings/global/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://javireguera.github.io/docs/settings/global/</guid><description>&lt;p>The global settings are stored in the settings.yaml file you can find one level above the language-specific settings.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="favicon-image">Favicon image&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>A website is not complete without a nice favicon image (shown in the address bar of your browser). Use an SVG image for the best result.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="color-name">Color name&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>You can set the color of the theme by entering a color name here. Currently &amp;lsquo;yellow&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;red&amp;rsquo; are supported. Note that you can also override this on each page by using the variable &lt;code>color_name&lt;/code> in the front matter. You can also &lt;a href="https://javireguera.github.io/docs/customizations/colors/">manually customize&lt;/a> the colors.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>General</title><link>https://javireguera.github.io/docs/settings/general/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://javireguera.github.io/docs/settings/general/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="title">Title&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>The title field holds the title of the website. This is used in the SEO title of the page and in the footer if you choose not to use a logo there.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="description">Description&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>The description is used for the meta description (SEO field) when the page has no (other) content.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="contact">Contact&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>The contact data for the contact buttons and the preheader are stored under &amp;lsquo;contact&amp;rsquo; in a &amp;lsquo;phone&amp;rsquo; and &amp;rsquo;email&amp;rsquo; variable.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Header</title><link>https://javireguera.github.io/docs/settings/header/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://javireguera.github.io/docs/settings/header/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="logo-image">Logo image&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>This sets the image in the header. Omitting a value here results in a &amp;rsquo;text logo&amp;rsquo; as you can see on this website. The text logo consists of the value in &lt;code>title&lt;/code> field that can be found in the &amp;lsquo;general.yaml&amp;rsquo; file in the data folder and the &lt;code>logo_subtitle&lt;/code> field that you can find in this data file.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="logo-subtitle">Logo subtitle&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>When you choose to omit the value for &lt;code>logo_image&lt;/code> the &amp;rsquo;text logo&amp;rsquo; will appear. The text logo consists of the value in &lt;code>title&lt;/code> field that can be found in the &amp;lsquo;general.yaml&amp;rsquo; file in the data folder and this &lt;code>logo_subtitle&lt;/code> field.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Footer</title><link>https://javireguera.github.io/docs/settings/footer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://javireguera.github.io/docs/settings/footer/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="logo-image">Logo image&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Here you can specify the path to the logo that should be displayed in the footer.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="menu-items">Menu items&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>This is an array that holds the footer menu. The items in this array consist of a &lt;code>title&lt;/code> and a &lt;code>link&lt;/code> field. In the title you put the page title and in link you put the relative url of that page.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="socials">Socials&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>This is an array that holds the social links. The items in this array consist of a &lt;code>title&lt;/code>, a &lt;code>link&lt;/code> and a &lt;code>logo&lt;/code> field. These links represent the social media platforms of your choice. The logo images should be black SVG&amp;rsquo;s an a transparent background.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>